hi this is Paul belmus your Sun Life
unit manager and this time I will
discuss financial advisor and what are
the benefits
or you want to spend more time with your
family
in this video
four major things
foreign
[Music]
and this is my team we are from
different walks of life so some here are
part-timers and some are full-timers
mission so as you can see
man my engineer my teachers no so we are
mostly Jency and Millennials
the team is 80 percent
so we reach out to our friends workmates
classmates colleagues and relatives and
we teach them the value of savings the
importance of insurance and the value of
investing in
case
so we recommend and offer Financial
plans
then whether it be a life insurance a
health insurance educational plans
retirement plans or pure Investments
thank you let's talk about
because
financial advisor is
financially secured
imagine in mono for example my
Breadwinner tapos
if something happens to him or her find
the name future
another example is
financially prepared by peace of mind
so what's in it for you do notice a
benefit
no this is a work from home
you can have more time
foreign
sales and personal development
as a person
we love team buildings
happy people are productive
so in our thing we love to
swimming the building
all this stuff available
incentives and bonuses
favorite
your purpose and advocacy
the greatest impacted
as financial advisors to deliver a
deadly since most of our product is a
life or health insurance
and just to share with you know
uh it's a personal story
my wife had cancer last temporarily
on
stressful because
so
it's the case insurance
[Music]
regular internet
so now for the question and answer no so
how do we earn bahas Financial advice or
first of all this is not for people who
are looking for fixed monthly income you
see that is for employment
Sun Life is a business financial advisor
is a sales career so it's like having
your own business
you earn commission in profit when a
client appears
foreign foreign
Improvement
for the qualifications
educational attainment is not really a
factor here in high school or college
undergrad command since this is a sales
career your positive attitude your
growth mindset and your if you're
comfortable talking to people that will
be your kids
so for the requirements this is a work
from home career so we require laptop PC
or iPad and stable internet at home so
smartphones are not counted
and financial advisors are professionals
and license so we undergo trainings and
licensure
as per the exam there is an example of
2020 pesos that's your business
so do you believe in what we do and do
you want to be part of this mission
number two do you have the heart to
serve people and you want to earn more
at the same time number three are you
coachable and you don't settle for
personal drama and excuses
and lastly do you think you deserve more
in life than what you have right now if
you answer yes to these questions then
I'll be happy to guide you and Coach you
sakare and for those
then maybe this is not the career not
pizza gifts and talents America
so if you want to proceed come back to
me message me again and say yes I mean
so this has been your unit manager Paul
bellness thank you everyone bye